http://www.collegerecruiter.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us and maintaining your trust is our priority. To ensure that your privacy choices are respected, College Recruiter, Inc. ("College Recruiter," "we," or "us") has set out in this Privacy Policy, an explanation of our online information practices as well as the decisions you may make regarding how your information is collected and used when viewing the www.CollegeRecruiter.com website and other College Recruiter-owned websites (collectively, the "Site").
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW WE COLLECT IT
We collect several types of information from and about users of the Site and the products and services of College Recruiter (collectively, the "Services"), including:
Information by which you can be personally identified, such as your name, physical address, e-mail address, and phone number ("Personal Information"). The specific Personal Information that we collect depends on the type of Services that you may be using; and
Information, which does not identify you ("Technical Information"). We collect this Technical Information:
directly from you when you provide it to us;
automatically as you navigate through the Site (e.g., usage details); and
from third parties, for example, our partners.
Your knowledge and consent of our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal information is critical in order for us to provide the Services to you. We rely on any of the following actions by you as indications of your consent to our existing and future Personal Information practices: your voluntary provision of Personal Information directly to us; your express consent or acknowledgement contained within a written, verbal or electronic application process; your consent solicited by us (or our agent) for a specified purpose; or your acceptance of the Privacy Policy until you notify us in writing of a withdrawal of this consent.
Information You Provide to Us.
In the course of using the Services, you may provide us with information about yourself, including, but not limited to:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site, responding to surveys, creating an account, subscribing to the Services, posting material, communicating with our personnel, sending, receiving, or engaging with messages, requesting further services, entering a contest, taking part in a promotion, or reporting a problem.
Details of transactions you carry out through our Site.
User Contributions, i.e., you may provide information to be published or displayed on public areas of the Site, or transmitted to other users of the Site or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions").
If you authorize College Recruiter to connect your account to the account of a "Connected Site" (e.g., LinkedIn, Monster, Facebook or Twitter), we may be able to access information you have provided to the Connected Site, such as content information, timeline feeds, contact and follow lists, network statistics and updates regarding your Connected Site account.
Information We Collect through Automatic Data Technologies. As you navigate through and interact with our Services, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:
Details of your visits to our Site and use of the Services, including traffic data, location data, logs and the resources that you access and use on our Site or the Services.
Information about your computer and internet connection, operating system and browser type, device identifier ("UDID") and your Internet Protocol (IP) address.
Location based information for the purpose of setting up your job search preferences.
2. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information:
To administer our Site and its contents to you.
To provide you with information, products or services that you need depending on the type of Services you use.
To provide you with notices about your account and/or your subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.
To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
To notify you about changes to our Site, products or services.
To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.
To diagnose service or technical problems, trouble shooting, analyzing how our Services is used, personalizing content for you, providing the end service to you (which may include sharing certain information with third party vendors and service providers) and to respond to any enquiries that you may have.
To improve our Site and the Services by enabling us to: store information about your preferences, allowing us to deliver a more personalized service to you; speed up your searches; and recognize you when you return to the Site.
In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
For any other purpose with your consent or which we, in our sole discretion, choose in order to deliver the Services.
IMPORTANT: Any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose for public posting to our Services, such as User Content, becomes available to the public and may be accessed, used and stored by others around the world. Accordingly, you should not post sensitive personal information or any other information that you would not want made public to any other Site or application or to a public website. You should never provide your social security number, national insurance number, financial information, passport number, and other sensitive information.
3. HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
Personal Information. We may share or disclose your Personal Information with selected third parties, including:
Companies with which we are affiliated, including but not limited to those within our corporate family.
To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets or stock, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by us about our Users is among the assets transferred.
To enforce or apply our Terms of Use Agreement or other agreements with you.
Law enforcement agencies; we fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our Services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of College Recruiter, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
If we believe that such action is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities (including instances where we suspect a User has uploaded any content that is infringing).
Third party vendors who we use to support our business and help provide end services to you, including, but not limited to, credit card processing and other billing service providers, customer service providers, messaging service providers, and email service providers. We may also authorize third party vendors to collect information on our behalf, including as necessary to operate certain features of our Site or to facilitate the delivery of online advertising tailored to your interests. Third-party vendors have access to and may collect information only as needed to perform their functions and are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose.
To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have consented to or not opted out of these disclosures.
To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an e-mail address to use the "e-mail a friend" feature of our Site, we will transmit the contents of that e-mail and your e-mail address to the recipients.
Prospective employers and other entities if you respond to a job advertisement or have opted-in to our Resume Database. Note: to the extent that you have an account with College Recruiter, please ensure that the resume associated with your account is up-to-date so when you apply for a job on a College Recruiter website, the employer receives your most recent resume. You will have an account with College Recruiter if you opened an account yourself, signed up for job alerts, submitted your resume to the resume database, and/or applied for a job on the College Recruiter website.
Upon your authorization, the Services may also post information directly to your account with College Recruiter.
Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our site.
Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score if this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.
With prospective employers or other entities if you add your resume to the Resume Database.
With prospective employers and other entities and/or with their external Applicant Tracking System or similar external system used by such companies to manage responses to their job postings.
From time to time, we may run contests, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on our Services together with a third-party partner. If you provide information to such third parties, you give them permission to use it for the purpose of that Event and any other use that you approve. We cannot control third parties' use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events.
For any other purpose with your consent or which we, in our sole discretion, choose in order to deliver the Services.
Technical Information. We may share Technical Information including but not limited to usage data and demographics, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, and number of clicks with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain College Recruiter services or to drive product engagement with other Users of the Services.
4. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION
We use appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect any Personal Information we process about you. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions and credit or debit card data will be encrypted.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that:
there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control;
the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed; and
any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone and keep your account information secure. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Site like message boards.
In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, College Recruiter will notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by applicable law.
5. PUBLIC FORUMS
You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose any Personal Information in a public forum on the Site, this information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such information. You accept that you, and not College Recruiter, are responsible for providing such information in any public forum. Any submissions to public areas on the Site are accepted by you with the understanding that such forums are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments or any content to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.
6. COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
Tracking Technologies. College Recruiter and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.
Blocking Cookies. You can also set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our Site through your access to some functionality and areas of our Site may be restricted. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information.
Passive Information. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.
To manage Flash LSOs please click here. We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Services or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on the Services and other sites in order to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you do not wish to have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note that this does not opt you out of being served generic ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Clear GIF's Information. When you use our Services, College Recruiter or our third-party analytics providers may employ clear GIF's (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users and help us better manage content on our Site by informing us of what content is effective. No personally identifiable information from your College Recruiter account is collected using these clear GIF's. In addition, we may also use clear GIF's in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make our Services better for our users. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.
Tracking Across Third-Party Websites. Some third-party websites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, certain website browsers allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked. The Services does not respond to Do Not Track ("DNT") signals on your browser. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
Push Notifications. We may send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.
7. SOCIAL MEDIA (FEATURES) AND WIDGETS
Our Services may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, and social sharing buttons or links. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Services, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing such features.
8. CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION INCLUDING MARKETING PREFERENCES
You may decline to submit Personal Information through our Services, in which case College Recruiter may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update, delete inaccuracies, or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging into your account and selecting email/password.
We cannot delete your Personal Information except by also deleting your user account. Please note, since we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Site. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups. We also reserve the right to retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to contact you via email, click "Unsubscribe" in any e-mail communications we send you. You cannot opt-out of Services-related notices. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, offers, or new features or functionality.
9. WHERE YOUR INFORMATION IS STORED
Please be aware that your Personal Information collected outside the U.S., is transferred to, stored in and processed in our facilities and by those third parties with whom we may share your Personal Information, in the United States and potentially in other countries. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
10. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
College Recruiter does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register to use the Services. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any Personal Information to College Recruiter or on the Site. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@CollegeRecruiter.com.
11. THIRD PARTY WEB SITES
Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites accessible through our Site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each website's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our Site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.
12. NOTIFICATION PROCEDURES
It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business-related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our Site, as determined by College Recruiter in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt-out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.
13. COLLEGE RECRUITER AS A DATA PROCESSOR
The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged College Recruiter.
College Recruiter acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. With respect to Personal Information provided by a client of ours (e.g., where we send job alert emails to job seekers on behalf of that client), we collect such information under the direction of that client and have no direct relationship with the individuals whose Personal Information we process. If you are a customer of such a College Recruiter client and would no longer like to be contacted by such client, please contact the client directly. If you seek access or want to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, you must direct your request to that College Recruiter client (the data controller). If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by our service agreements with our Clients.
We will retain Personal Information that we process on behalf of our clients for as long as needed to provide services to our client. College Recruiter will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and in accordance with our internal record keeping policies.
14. Contact
If you have questions about your User account, your subscription plan, job alerts, applications to Job Advertisements, or any other Services-related questions, please contact Customer Service by email at support@CollegeRecruiter.com; call 952.848.2211; or letter to College Recruiter, Inc., 7201 York Ave South Ste 410, Minneapolis, MN 55435-4441.
